In this screencast we're going to show the basics of navigation in IntelliJ IDEA
在此截屏视频中，我们将展示IntelliJ IDEA中的导航基础
This is the default setup when you start IntelliJ IDEA
这是启动IntelliJ IDEA时的默认设置
Note that you have some navigation hints here, and we'll see some of these in action
请注意，您这里有一些导航提示，我们将在其中看到其中一些
IntelliJ IDEA has a navigation bar at the
IntelliJ IDEA的导航栏位于
top, a series of tool window buttons along the edges which let you open a window, the
顶部，沿着边缘的一系列工具窗口按钮，这些按钮可让您打开一个窗口，
main project window on the left, which you can navigate using the mouse, the keyboard,
左侧的主项目窗口，您可以使用鼠标，键盘，
or even typing to search for something.
甚至输入搜索内容。
When you open a file, the editor opens the file and displays a tab.
打开文件时，编辑器将打开文件并显示一个选项卡。
Each new file has a new tab.
每个新文件都有一个新标签。
The editor also shows a breadcrumb trail to show where you are in the file
编辑器还会显示面包屑痕迹，以显示您在文件中的位置
We can use these mechanisms to navigate in
我们可以使用这些机制来导航
IntelliJ IDEA, but all of these things take up valuable screen space which we'd prefer
IntelliJ IDEA，但所有这些都占用了宝贵的屏幕空间，我们更喜欢
to use for showing code.
用于显示代码。
Let's get set up with the advanced mode of using IntelliJ IDEA, which relies on just
让我们设置使用IntelliJ IDEA的高级模式，该模式仅依赖于
keyboard shortcuts
键盘快捷键
First, lets turn off the breadcrumbs.
首先，让我们关闭面包屑。
We can do this using the settings window by searching for breadcrumbs and turning them
我们可以使用设置窗口来执行此操作，方法是搜索面包屑并将其旋转
off, you can see they're no longer shown at the bottom of the editor.
关闭，您可以看到它们不再显示在编辑器的底部。
But there's a simpler way to change a setting.
但是，有一种更简单的方法可以更改设置。
We can use Shift Ctrl A or Shift Cmd A to find an action, and type the name of the setting.
我们可以使用Shift Ctrl A或Shift Cmd A查找操作，然后键入设置的名称。
To turn off tabs, type tab and set tab placement to None.
要关闭选项卡，请键入选项卡，然后将选项卡位置设置为“无”。
We can also turn off the navigation bar and
我们还可以关闭导航栏，然后
the tool window buttons this way.
工具窗口按这种方式按钮。
Finally, to get the most screen space for
最后，获得最大的屏幕空间
the editor we use Shift Ctrl F12 or Shift Cmd F12 to hide all the side windows and expand
编辑器，我们使用Shift Ctrl F12或Shift Cmd F12隐藏所有侧面窗口并展开
the editor
编辑
How do we move around now?
我们现在该如何走动？
With a set of keyboard shortcuts.
带有一组键盘快捷键。
There are a lot of different ways to move around, we can use the ones that are most
有很多不同的移动方式，我们可以使用最有效的方式。
useful to us
对我们有用
Firstly, Alt plus a number, or Cmd plus a number, opens up the tool windows.
首先，Alt加一个数字，或Cmd加一个数字，打开工具窗口。
For example, Alt + 1 for the project window, Alt + 9 for the VCS window.
例如，项目窗口为Alt + 1，VCS窗口为Alt + 9。
Escape moves the focus from that window back to the editor, and of course we can use shift
Escape将焦点从该窗口移回编辑器，我们当然可以使用shift
Ctrl F12 again to hide the windows.
再次按F12隐藏窗口。
If a window doesn't have a number, or we forget
如果窗口没有数字，或者我们忘记了
what it is, we can use Ctrl E or Cmd E to bring up the recent files list, which also
这是什么，我们可以使用Ctrl E或Cmd E调出最近的文件列表，
shows all the available windows.
显示所有可用的窗口。
Like all IntelliJ IDEA windows, typing here allows us to search.
像所有IntelliJ IDEA窗口一样，在此处键入内容使我们可以搜索。
We can use the recent files window to quickly
我们可以使用“最近的文件”窗口快速
move to a file we've been to lately, and we can even use CamelCase to search these files
移至我们最近去过的文件，甚至可以使用CamelCase搜索这些文件
for the one we want.
对于我们想要的那个。
Shift Ctrl E or Shift Cmd E brings up a list
Shift Ctrl E或Shift Cmd E弹出一个列表
of recent locations - This isn't just a file but a location within a file, so we can navigate
最近位置-这不仅是文件，而且是文件中的位置，因此我们可以进行导航
directly to a recent snippet of code
直接到最近的一段代码
Often we know the exact name of the class we want to open, we can use Ctrl N or Cmd O
通常我们知道要打开的类的确切名称，我们可以使用Ctrl N或Cmd O
to open a search for classes.
打开课程搜索。
We could type the name of the class in here until just the option we want is available,
我们可以在此处输入类的名称，直到只有我们想要的选项可用为止，
or we can use camel case or even partial class names to locate a class that matches.
或者我们可以使用驼峰式大小写，甚至使用局部类名来查找匹配的类。
If we want to open a file that isn't a Java class, we can use Shift Ctrl N or
如果要打开不是Java类的文件，可以使用Shift Ctrl N或
Shift Cmd O to navigate to a file.
Shift Cmd O导航到文件。
With classes or files we can type a colon followed by a line number and we can go straight
使用类或文件，我们可以在输入冒号后加上行号，然后直接输入
to that line in the file.
到文件中的那一行。
If we know the name of the method we want,
如果我们知道所需方法的名称，
we can use navigate to symbol, Shift Ctrl Alt N or Alt Cmd O and type the method name.
我们可以使用导航到符号，Shift Ctrl Alt N或Alt Cmd O并输入方法名称。
Again, camel case and partial names are supported.
同样，支持驼峰大小写和部分名称。
We can also add a class name or partial class name to search for symbols within a
我们还可以添加一个类名或部分类名来搜索
specific namespace
特定名称空间
Once we're inside the code, we can navigate to a declaration using Ctrl B or Cmd B.
进入代码后，可以使用Ctrl B或Cmd B导航到声明。
We can also easily navigate back to where we cam from using Ctrl Alt Left or Cmd Alt left arrow.
我们还可以使用Ctrl Alt Left或Cmd Alt向左箭头轻松导航回到我们的摄影位置。
We can navigate forward using Ctrl Alt Right or Cmd Alt right arrow.
我们可以使用Ctrl Alt向右箭头或Cmd Alt向右箭头导航。
If we're working with interfaces, navigating
如果我们正在使用接口，请导航
to the declaration might not be that useful.
声明可能没有那么有用。
We can use ctrl alt b or alt cmd b to navigate to an implementation.
我们可以使用ctrl alt b或alt cmd b导航到一个实现。
If there's just one implementation, we'll move straight to that implementation.
如果只有一个实现，我们将直接转到该实现。
If there's more than one, we see a list like this and we can select the one we want.
如果有多个，我们会看到这样的列表，我们可以选择所需的列表。
Let's use navigate to declaration to go to
让我们使用导航到声明去
the declaration that uses the interface.
使用接口的声明。
If we move the caret onto the interface name, we can use Alt F7 to find the usages of this
如果将插入符号移动到接口名称上，则可以使用Alt F7查找此符号的用法。
interface, which lists everywhere that calls methods on the interface as well as implementation
接口，其中列出了调用接口方法以及实现的所有地方
of the interface.
接口的。
This can be another useful way to navigate to relevant classes from the code that uses them.
这是从使用它们的代码导航到相关类的另一种有用的方法。
If we're doing test driven development we
如果我们正在进行测试驱动的开发，我们
may find another method of navigation helpful.
可能会发现另一种导航方法很有帮助。
If we're inside a test class and press shift Ctrl T, or Shift Cmd T, we will move into
如果我们在测试班级内，然后按Shift Ctrl T或Shift Cmd T，我们将进入
the class that the test is testing.
测试正在测试的类。
If we're in a class and we want to move to the test, or to see if it has a test, we can
如果我们正在上课，并且想要进行测试，或者想看看它是否有测试，我们可以
use the same key combination to see the tests and select one, or even create a new test.
使用相同的组合键查看测试并选择一个，甚至创建一个新测试。
If all this is a bit too much to remember,
如果这一切让您难以忘怀，
there's a simple shortcut for everything - double tap shift and we get the search everywhere box.
一切都有一个简单的捷径-点按两次即可找到“随处搜索”框。
This lists the recent files by default, and we can optionally narrow down our search choices
默认情况下，这会列出最近的文件，我们可以选择缩小搜索范围
if we want to.
如果我们愿意。
Type anything in there and it will give a list of files, actions, classes, symbols,
在其中输入任何内容，它将提供文件，操作，类，符号，
and settings.
和设置。
Use forward slash to see the commands, selecting one of these will give a list of appropriate options.
使用正斜杠查看命令，选择其中一个将给出适当选项的列表。
If you find there's something you search for
如果您找到要搜索的内容
fairly frequently that doesn't easily show up in the results, you could of course, create
经常不容易出现在结果中，您当然可以创建
a keyboard shortcut for it.
键盘快捷键。
But you can also add an abbreviation, or keyword, to make it easier to find.
但是，您也可以添加缩写或关键字，以使其更易于查找。
Search for the action in the keymap, press enter to bring up the menu on the item, select
在键盘图中搜索动作，按Enter调出项目菜单，选择
Add Abbreviation, and type the keyword you want to use in the search.
添加缩写，然后键入要在搜索中使用的关键字。
Then, when you double tap shift to bring up the search, you can type this abbreviation
然后，当您点按两次Shift键以显示搜索内容时，可以键入此缩写
and the action should be the first item in the list.
并且该动作应该是列表中的第一项。
Finally, there's one last area where keyboard
最后是键盘的最后一个区域
shortcuts can be much quicker than using the navigation bar.
快捷方式比使用导航栏要快得多。
We can run anything from anywhere inside the IDE by double tapping ctrl.
通过双击ctrl，我们可以在IDE中的任何位置运行任何东西。
This brings up a list of recently run tests or applications, and we can type the name
这将显示最近运行的测试或应用程序的列表，我们可以输入名称
of any run configuration to find it and run it.
找到并运行它的任何运行配置。
This is a fast way to start a test or service without having to navigate to the file itself
这是启动测试或服务的快速方法，而无需导航到文件本身
or use the navigation bar.
或使用导航栏。
Ctrl and F2 or Cmd F2 brings up a list of processes we can stop
Ctrl和F2或Cmd F2弹出一个我们可以停止的进程列表
or we can press Ctrl F2 a second time to stop all processes
或者我们可以再次按Ctrl F2来停止所有进程
In summary, the easiest way to navigation around IntelliJ IDEA is using the keyboard.
总之，在IntelliJ IDEA上导航的最简单方法是使用键盘。
This is much faster than using the mouse, and allows us to free up valuable screen space
这比使用鼠标快得多，并且使我们可以释放宝贵的屏幕空间
for the code we're working on.
我们正在处理的代码。
Thanks for watching!
感谢收看！